天啊  能和你一起玩  真是太棒了
Man, this is so great, getting to hang out with you.
你是多么好的一个人啊
I forgot how cool you are.
噢  艾薇  你真好
Aww. Ivy, you are so sweet.
我也喜欢和你一起玩
I love hanging out with you too.
嘘  俺在视频聊天呢
Shh! I'm on video chat.
噢  嘿  艾薇  你收到指导员发的邮件了吗
Oh! Hey, Ivy, did you see this email from our guidance counselor?
没有  如果是学校的邮件  直接扔进垃圾邮件里
Mm-mm. If it's from school, it goes straight to my spam.
你看  这是关于咱们社区服务的要求
Well, this is about our community service requirement.
如果不完成这项  咱们明年就不能毕业
If we don't get this done, we don't graduate next year.
看  这就是为什么俺从来不看这些邮件
See? This is why I don't open emails from school.
总想把俺逼疯
They always stress me out.
噢不  大事不妙啊
Oh no, it gets worse.
看  因为我们下手慢了
See, because we waited so long,
现在只剩两个劳动岗位了
There are only two jobs left.
第一个的劳动内容包括帮助老人
The first one includes helping old people...
-算了  -你还没听我说完呢
-Pass. -But you didn't let me finish.
俺听到“老人”就放弃了
You lost me at "old people."
另一个呢
so what's the other one?
在K魁实习
Interning at k-qui,
-那个公共广播电台  -你是说那个
-That public radio station. -You mean the one where...
每个人都这么说话的电台吗
Everyone talks like this.
是的  是的  就是那个
Yes. Yes, that's the one.
天啊  俺讨厌那个电台
Man, I hate that station.
好吧  那你愿意给老人搓澡吗
Well, would you rather bathe old people?
还是去电台吧
And we're on the air.
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  liloelva
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第三集
Good Luck Charlie  S03E03  Amy Needs a Showe
嘿  老鲍亲  我有个主意
Hey, Bob, honey, I have a great idea.
-我们应该弄个孩子  -打住
-We should have a baby... -No!
孩子够多了
No more babies!
能让我把话说完嘛
Would you let me finish?
我想说我们应该弄个孩子迎接派对
I was going to say we should have a baby <i>shower.</i>
噢
Oh.
你说话不要大喘气
You should really run your words together a little faster.
都第五个孩子了  再开个婴儿洗礼还合适吗
Is a baby shower even appropriate for a fifth kid?
当你把所有婴儿用品扔掉的时候  是合适的
It is when you gave away all your other baby stuff.
因为你斩钉截铁的认为
Because you were absolutely certain.
我们不会再生孩子了
You weren't gonna have another one.
你看我干什么
What are you looking at me for?
这么说来
So...
给自己开一个婴儿洗礼  对吧
Throwing yourself a baby shower, huh?
我才没有给自己办个婴儿洗礼
I am not throwing myself a baby shower.
多俗气  我只是需要
That's tacky. I just need.
哄骗某人帮我办一个
To trick someone into throwing it for me.
到底是谁呢
But who?
噢  您歇着  我去开门
Oh, don't worry. I'll get it.
-嗨  -玛丽露·温兹太太
-Hi. -Mary Lou Wentz.
请进吧
Come on in.
谢谢  艾米
Thank you, Amy.
我刚才还和老鲍谈到你呢
I was just talking to Bob about you.
-是吗  -我就是跟他说说
-Really? -I was just telling him.
你是多么好的一位知己啊
How you're my very best friend.
噢
Oh.
你是我的
And you're...
我只是过来接艾薇的
I'm just here to pick up Ivy.
玛丽露  急什么
Mary Lou, what's the rush?
坐下  歇会
Have a seat. Take a load off.
噢  我就不打扰你俩聊天了
Oh, I think I'm just gonna leave you two alone.
我的知己最近在忙些什么啊
So what's my best friend up to?
我的知己就是你
That would be you.
噢  对  对
Oh, right right.
那个  不怎么忙
Well, not much.
不错  不错
Great great.
和你说一下  如果你想找点事情做
Well, you know, if you want something to do,
你可以帮你的知己办个婴儿洗礼啊
You could throw a baby shower for your best friend.
你的知己就是我
That would be me.
噢  婴儿洗礼
Oh. A baby shower?
是啊  是不是挺有趣的
Yes, doesn't it sound fun?
听着  我来操办所有事情
Okay, I will do all the work.
你只需要露露脸  然后主持一下
All you have to do is show up and host it.
好吧  这个我没问题
Okay, I guess I could do that.
太好了
Great.
噢  我希望是个惊喜派对
Oh, and I want it to be a surprise.
但你已经知道这件事了
But you already know about it.
我们不是正在谈这件事呢吗
I mean we're talking about it right now.
噢  玛丽大姐
Oh, Mary Lou,
亲啊  我是实力派演员
Honey, I'm an incredible actress,
不信你试试  呃  跟我说些伤心事
try me. Just, umm, tell me something sad.
呃  你的狗生病了
Um, your dog is sick.
什么  不要啊
What? No!
我活不了了
I can't bear it!
不  为什么啊  噢  为什么
No! Why? Oh why?
艾薇
Ivy!
嘿
Hey.
好消息  我的朋友里奇得了肾结石
Great news! My friend Richie's got a kidney stone.
好耶  耶
Yes! Yeah!
等等  为什么是好消息
Wait. Why is that great news?
因为他不能拿着他的两张前排票去看冰球了
Because he can't use his front-row tickets to the hockey game.
也就是说我可以带你俩中的其中一个  跟我一起去
Which means I get to go and I get to bring one of you.
-噢  带我去  带我去  -噢  好吧
-Oh! Take me! Take me! -Okay, all right.
你俩自己解决这件事
You guys need to work this out,
因为我不能偏心
Because I can't pick a favorite.
我是说  虽然我心里有数
I mean, I've got one,
但我不能说出来
I just can't say who it is.
好了  嘿  我有个主意
Okay. Hey, I've got an idea.
抛硬币  如何
We'll flip a coin, all right?
头朝上  我赢  尾巴朝上  你输
Heads I win, tails you lose.
不  不  不  不  不
No no. No no no no no.
虽然我不知道其中有什么猫腻
I'm not sure what's wrong about that,
但是我确定我肯定会被骗
But I know I'm being tricked.
好吧  我在脑子里想一个数字
Okay, I'll think of a number in my head.
然后我们来猜个数  看谁接近
And we'll guess and see who comes the closest.
盖比  你已经用这个伎俩蒙过我一回了
Gabe, I'm not falling for that again.
-好吧  -出于猎奇  是不是六
-Fine. -Out of curiosity, was it six?
-是  -该死  嗯
-Yup. -Dang it! Mmm!
现在  让我们把目光转向
And now let's take a look.
国内新闻
At our national news.
好了  记住
Okay, so remember,
如果我们要拿下这份工作  就要用睿智取胜
If we're gonna get these jobs, we've gotta come across as smart.
所以我们喜欢看书  我们喜欢歌剧
So we love books, we love opera,
关于歌剧的书  关于书的歌剧
Books about opera, operas about books.
好了  明白了  明白了
Right, got it, got it.
-好的  -要表现得聪明秃顶
-Yeah. -Act all brainyish and stuff.
你还是别说话了
And let me do the talking.
立法机关的众议院
The lower House of the legislature.
以92对68的票选通过该法案
Passed the bill by a vote of 92-68.
并送去上议院
And then it was sent to the upper chamber.
后续还将有更多关于此则新闻的报道
More to come on this fast-breaking story.
这里是K魁电台
This is k-qui,
一个安静的电台
The quiet station.
-你们好啊  姑娘们  -嗨
-Well, hello, girls. -Hi.
我是黛安·范德外丝
I'm Diane Vanderweis,
站长兼DJ
Station manager and on-air personality.
噢  我叫泰迪  幸会
Oh, I'm Teddy. Charmed.
俺是艾薇
And I'm Ivy.
借用威廉·莎士比亚的一句话“你好”
As William Shakespeare once said, "hello."
莎士比亚的确说过这句话
Well, I'm sure he did say that at some point.
噢  没错  他说过  我们在书中读到过
Oh yes, he... he did. We looked it up in a book.
并且在歌剧中也有听到
And heard it in an opera.
好吧  跟我说说
Okay. So tell me,
你们对KQUI熟悉吗
And you familiar with k.Q.U.I.?
-不熟悉  是什么  -噢  呃
-No, what's that? -Oh, uh...
她开玩笑呢  她当然知道KQUI
She's kidding. She knows that k.Q.U.I.
不就是咱们面试的电台吗  对吧  艾薇
Is the radio station that we are in. Right, Ivy?
借用威廉·莎士比亚的一句话“是的”
As William Shakespeare once said, "yes."
好吧  你们听说过
Okay. Have you heard.
我们的招牌节目“水果漫谈”
Our award-winning program "fruit talk"?
噢  “水果漫谈”啊  知道  我喜欢那节目
Oh, "fruit talk." yeah, I love that show.
鲜嫩多汁而且夸夸其谈
I find it both fruity and talky.
好吧  那就太好了
Well, that's great,
因为我准备让你们来接手这个节目
Because that's the show you're going to be working on.
欢迎来到K魁大家庭  姑娘们
Welcome to the k-qui family, girls.
谢谢  黛安
Thank you, Diane.
我们  我们真的很开心
We are... we're really very excited.
嗯  您能先把学校这东西签了吗
Mm-hmm. Now can you just sign this form for school?
你们工作结束后  我再签
I sign that after you do the work.
试试也无妨啊
It was worth a shot.
-嘿  -嘿  亲爱的
-Hey. -Hey, honey.
-干啥呢  -为了婴儿洗礼
-What you doing? -Making out the guest list.
弄一下宾客名单
For my baby shower.
你邀请了你的前老板凯伦
You're inviting your ex-boss Karen?
-我以为你不待见她呢  -亲爱的  我是不待见她
-I thought you didn't like her? -Honey, I can't stand her.
但是你也知道  她傍了个大款
But you know, she married a rich guy.
也就是说  送的礼物将价值不菲
And that means an expensive present.
我喜欢礼物
I like presents.
查莉  拜托了  宝贝  别这么贪婪  好不
Charlie. Please, honey, don't be greedy, okay?
这个派对是给我的
This party's for mommy.
等等  为什么黛比·杜利画了个问号
Wait. Why is Debbie Dooley a question mark?
亲啊  因为我不知道是否能忍受她的声音
'Cause, hovey, I'm not sure I can handle the voice.
我是黛比·杜利  你们好呀
I'm Debbie Dooley. How ya doin'?
噢  让我头疼
Oh, it gives me a headache.
-那你不打算邀请她了  -噢  邀请她
-So you're not inviting her? -Oh, I'm inviting her.
这女的会烘焙  当然了  你肯定逃不过她的魔音
The girl can bake. Of course, then you have to hear her say
“这是小饼干  只给亲们吃啊”
"Here's a snickerdoodle just for you-dle."
现在我要做的就是把宾客名单电邮给玛丽露
Now all I have to do is email this list to Mary Lou,
然后她就会回复给我一堆笑脸表情
And then she can reply with a bunch of smiley faces.
噢  那女人真是太得意洋洋了
Oh, that woman is too perky.
好吧  我们有
Okay, so we've got...
我们有得意洋洋的人  有烦人的人
We got too perky, we got too annoying.
有你忍受不了的人
And we got somebody that you can't stand.
看起来这个派对够悲剧的
This sounds like an awful party.
老鲍  别这样  他们是我最亲爱的朋友了
Bob, please, these are my dearest friends you're talking about.
嘿  老爸
Hey, dad.
PJ
P.J.
-你看起来不错啊  -嗯
-You're looking well. -Mmm.
嘿  好消息
Hey, great news,
我和盖比把问题解决了  我们决定
Gabe and I worked it out, and we decided.
我和你一起去看比赛
That I would be going to the game with you.
-只有你吗  -恩  是的
-Just you. -Mm-hmm. That's right.
-恩  -嘿
-Mmm. -Hey.
同志们  对不起了  我只能带一个人去
Guys, I'm sorry. I can only take one of you.
-带我  -不  不  带我
-Take me. -No no, take me.
-我爱你更深  -不对  我爱你更深
-I love you more. -No, I love you more.
-嘿  嘿  嘿  -不  我爱你更深
-Hey hey hey! -No, I love you more.
我曾梦想过你们能有这样的争论
I have dreamed of you guys having this argument...
但不是你们穿一条裤子的时候
Just not while you're wearing the same pants.
我是黛比·杜利  你好呀
I'm Debbie Dooley. How ya doin'?
玛丽露·温兹  欢迎光临
Mary Lou Wentz. Welcome.
抱歉我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
遇到下班晚高峰了
The commute was a bear.
噢  我还以为你住在街对面呢
Oh. I thought you lived across the street.
没错  骗到你了吧
I do. Gotcha!
-艾米来了  -噢  大家藏好
-Here comes Amy! -Ooh! Everybody hide!
我的观音菩萨  太刺激了
Oh my goodness. This is so exciting.
我不知道藏
I don't know where to hi...
惊喜
Surprise!
什  什么啊
Wha... what is this?
给我开的派对吗
A party for me?
我  我都不知道该说什么了
I... I don't know what to say.
亲娘咧  太好玩了
Oh my gosh, this is so funny.
你们真是给了我一个大惊喜
You guys really got me.
现在我有点情绪激动
And now I'm getting emotional.
婴儿洗礼
A shower?
为了我的五号宝宝
For my fifth baby?
我都觉着不合适了
It almost seems inappropriate.
我被邀请的时候就是这么想的
That's what I thought when I got the invite.
噢  凯伦  真高兴你能来
Oh, Karen, I'm so glad you could make it.
噢  说实话  我最近接到了各种邀请
Oh, well, I've been getting invited to a lot of things lately.
不知道你有没有听说  我结婚了
I don't know if you've heard, but I married well.
哇  厉害  都把我闪瞎了
Whoa. Yes, that's very sparkly as well.
我很喜欢你的礼物
I'm just glad to have your present...
你的出席  很高兴你的到来
You present... I'm glad you're here.
好了  玛丽露
So, Mary Lou,
你都准备了什么洗礼游戏啊
What fun shower games did you plan?
洗礼游戏  你说我只要露露练就可以啊
Shower games? You said just show up.
什么  你说寻宝游戏吗
Well, a treasure hunt you say?
噢  哇
Oh wow.
噢  玛丽露  你还打印了地图啊
Oh, Mary Lou, you printed maps and everything?
哇  玛丽露  你的婴儿洗礼办的还真不赖
Wow, Mary Lou, you sure know how to throw a shower.
是啊  我花了不少的心血啊
Well, I put a lot of work into it.
成了  把戏份留给我
Yeah, leave the acting to me.
我是迈克·加拿格  你在收听的是
I'm Mike Cannagher, and you're listening.
“水果漫谈”中的一个
To a very special edition.
特别版块
Of "Fruit talk."
一个苹果激情秀
It's an apple-palooza.
苹果  苹果  苹果
Apples, apples, apples.
各种各样的苹果
All different kinds of apples.
富士苹果
Fuji.
瑞光苹果
Rome.
粉红女士苹果
Pink lady.
麦金托什红苹果
Mcintosh!
俺绝对熬不过五个小时
I'll never make it through five hours of this.
不成  我们必须熬  艾薇  如果我们没拿到
Well, we have to, Ivy. If we don't get.
签字  我们就不能毕业
That form signed, we don't graduate.
蛇果
<i>Red delicious.</i>
青苹果  布瑞本苹果
Granny Smith. Braeburn.
再说了  大不了不毕业
Then again, graduation's overrated.
现在真希望能待在家里参加婴儿洗礼
Now I'm kinda wishing we stayed at the baby shower.
我是说  那个虽然无聊  但是这个更无聊
I mean, it looked boring, but not this boring.
情况一定要好转啊
It's gotta get better.
等等  怎么没声音了
Wait, we're not getting any sound.
跟你说过情况好转了
Told you it'd get better.
也许麦克风挂了
Maybe the mic's dead.
不是  是迈克挂了
No, Mike's dead.
迈克
Mike?
-感觉好点了吗  迈克  -噢  还好
-Feeling better, Mike? -Oh, I'm fine.
只是因为那个苹果激情秀
It's just the apple-palooza...
太刺激了
Too much excitement.
等等  迈克  在你走之前  还有件事
Wait. Mike, before you go, one more thing...
-能把这个签了吗  -你俩要做完剩下的节目
-Could you sign this? -Well, you two are gonna have to do the rest of the show.
-什么  -噢  别担心
-What? -Oh, don't worry.
-只有四个小时  -可是  我们不知道怎么做啊
-It's only four hours. -Well, we don't know how to do this.
-知道苹果为何物吗  -知道
-You know what an apple is? -Yes.
那就成了
You're all set.
你找我们吗  老爸
You wanted to see us, dad?
PJ  盖比
P.J., Gabe,
快过来
Come on down!
-搞毛啊  -你是“幸运52”节目的
-What's all this? -You're the next contestants.
下一位选手
On "love that Bob."
这个游戏我们将揭晓
This is the game where we find out.
谁最了解老鲍
Who knows the most about Bob.
为您呈现的是  鲍勃到  害虫光
Brought to you by Bob's bugs be gone.
让我们见识下选手吧
And let's meet our contestants!
我是PJ
I'm P.J.
盖比
Gabe.
我喜欢你的激情
Love that enthusiasm.
好了  PJ  盖比
All right. P.J., Gabe,
我将问你们一些问题
I'm going to ask you a series of questions.
关于你们的父亲  也就是害虫控制专家鲍伯·邓肯
About your father, pest control specialist Bob Duncan.
答对题目最多者
Whoever winds up with the most correct answers.
将赢得一张冰球门票
Wins a ticket to a hockey game.
好了  让我们开始吧
All right, let's dive right in.
第一题
Question one,
-“鲍伯最喜欢”  -“甜甜圈”
-"what is Bob's"... -Donuts!
正确
Correct!
第二题
Second question...
匹萨
Pizza.
耶
Yeah.
让我们看一看不关于食物的题目
Let's move on from the food category.
好了  这有  这有一道简单的
Okay, here's... here's an easy one.
“鲍勃的中间名字是什么”
"what is Bob's middle name?"
到底是什么呢
Looking for a middle name.
好了  时间到
All right, time's up.
是威廉  下一道
It's William. Moving on.
“威廉·下一道”吗
"William moving on"?
这么恶心的名字
Yeesh, what a terrible name.
怪不得你以前没提到过
It's no wonder you never use it.
真想不到我会答不上来
I can't possibly lose this thing.
好了  这还有一道简单的
Okay, here's another easy one.
“鲍伯多大了”
"how old is Bob?"
五
Fift...
-六  -不对  不对  不对
-Six... -No no no.
-七  -好吧  下一题
-Seven... -All right, next question!
鲍伯是哪天的生日
When is Bob's birthday?
噢  不会吧  你们俩  应该知道这道题啊
Oh, come on, you guys. You gotta know this one.
一月一日
January 1st.
一月二日
January 2nd.
一月三日
January 3rd.
一月四日
January 4th.
好吧  我们来进入
Okay, we are now into our...
第二个小时的苹果激情秀
Second hour of apple-palooza.
依旧等候第一位打进电话的听众
Still waiting for that first call.
噢  提醒一下
Oh, just a reminder,
“激情秀”的意思是刺激
"palooza" means excitement,
而“打电话”的意思是“打电话”
And "call" means <i>call.</i>
任何人
Anyone.
任何人都可以打电话
Anyone at all.
噢  嘿  说到这  我们为何不疯狂一下呢
Oh, hey. In fact, why don't we just go crazy,
打开话匣子谈一谈美食
Open it up to foods of all kinds.
我们可以聊
We could talk...
蔬菜  牛排
Vegetables, steak,
香肠  培根
Sausage, bacon.
老爹  如果你在收听  请打电话
Dad, if you're out there, please call.
好了  查莉
Okay, Charlie,
你准备好帮助我拆礼物了吗
You ready to help mommy open her presents?
-好了  妈咪  -噢
-Yes, mommy. -Aww.
我知道你们在想什么
I know what you're all thinking.
我生了个超萌的孩子
I make the most adorable children.
超生游击队
And lots of 'em.
好了  在我们拆礼物之前  我先去
Okay, before we do presents, I'm just gonna run.
妈咪的小屋里一趟  马上回来
To the little mommy's room. Be right back.
-噢  -噢
-Oh. -Oh.
多漂亮的小丫头啊
What a pretty girl you are.
我叫凯伦
My name is Karen.
我妈咪不喜欢你
My mommy doesn't like you.
噢  天啊  她肯定喜欢我
Oh. Oh my. Of course she does.
要不然她怎么邀请我来派对啊
Why else would she invite me to the party?
你有钱
You're rich.
噢  嗯
Oh. Mm-hmm.
好吧  我承认  我有钱
Well, yes, I am rich,
也就意味着我有一辆大车
Which means I have a large car.
载着我的大礼物
To put my large present into.
然后开回家
And drive away!
好吧  够尴尬的
Well, that was awkward.
我确定你妈咪是喜欢我的  对吧  查莉
I'm certainly glad your mommy likes me. Huh, Charlie?
我妈说你说话很逗
My mom says you talk funny.
-什么  -让她头疼
-Pardon me? -It hurts her head.
-是吗  -是的
-Really? -Yeah.
好吧  那我只好带着我的小饼干
Well, I guess I'll just take my snickerdoodles.
开溜了
And skidoodle.
-你要走吗  -噢  那还用说
-You're leaving? -Oh, you betcha.
呃  艾米  我认为你应该快点过来
Uh, Amy, I think you might wanna hurry it up in there!
小气
Mean.
傻
Stupid.
臭
Smelly.
拜拜
Bye-bye.
好吧  现在的话题是
Okay, the topic is now
“世界上存在的
"things that exist.
东西”
In the world."
哇  好像我们接到了第一个电话
Wow, looks like we're getting an actual call.
嗨  欢迎致电“水果漫谈”  您是哪位
Hi, and welcome to "fruit talk. " who is this?
艾薇
It's Ivy.
你意识到咱们俩是唯一
You do realize we're the only ones.
听这节目的人吗
Listening to the show, right?
甚至连我都没在听
And I'm not even listening.
但是  我们还剩三个小时呢
Well, we still have three more hours to fill.
-你有什么办法吗  -不如这样
-What do you suggest? -How about this?
噢  好吧
Oh, okay.
我们试着水果漫谈  我们试着讨论话题
we tried to talk fruit, we tried some conversation
但是电台太无聊  我需要放松一下下
but the station's so boring, I need a vacation
听好了  同志们  这个电台衰到爆
Listen up, people, this station's a loser
整个节目就是一个苹果催眠秀
And this whole show was an apple-pa-snooza
-这个电台够悲催  -这个电台够腻人
-This station is sad. -This station is tired...
这两位实习生刚被炒鱿鱼了
<i>Said the two interns</i> <i>who just got fired.</i>
能先把这个签了吗
Can you sign this first?
七月七日
July 7th.
-七月八日  -七月九日
-July 8th. -July 9th.
成了  知道吗
All right, you know what?
这个  这个没有我想象中的有意思
This, uh... this wasn't as much fun as I thought it was gonna be.
看来我应该问问其他人想去看冰球比赛吗
I think I'm gonna ask somebody else to go to the hockey game.
哇  等等  别急  老爸  让我说句话
Whoa. Wait wait, dad, just let me say something.
七月十号
July 10th.
这次的婴儿洗礼简直就是场灾难
This shower was a total disaster.
我低估了查莉的理解能力
I guess Charlie understands more than I thought.
对不起  妈妈
I'm sorry, mama.
宝贝  没关系
Honey, it's okay.
没关系的  这不是你的错
It's okay. It's not your fault.
不是任何人的错
It's not anybody's fault.
-这个嘛  其实  -任何人都没有错玛丽露
-Well, actually... -It's not anybody's fault, Mary lo...
-好吧  -想来杯茶吗
-Okay. -Now would you like a cup of tea?
-好吧  麻烦你了  -没事
-Yes, I would love that. -Okay.
好了  一吐为快  查莉  她是怎么说我的
Okay, spill it, Charlie. What did she say about me?
也许你应该和我一起来
Maybe you should come with me.
好了  查莉  艾薇和我在找新的实习工作
Well, Charlie, Ivy and I are looking for a new internship,
而且  噢  我们在你周围所说的一字一句
And... oh, I guess we have to be more careful.
都应该小心一点
With what we say around you.
否则  人们就会知道他们太得意洋洋了
Otherwise, people might find out they're too <i>perky.</i>
您是来接艾薇的吗  温兹夫人
Are you here to pick up Ivy, Mrs. Wentz?
不是  我只是特别的烦人
No, I'm just <i>really</i> annoyed.
好吧
All righty, then.
好了  泰迪  别弄了  快走
Okay, Teddy, come on! Let's go.
我要去看我的第一场冰球比赛了
So I'm going to my first hockey game,
因为我是唯一知道老爸生日的孩子
'cause I was the only kid who knew when dad's birthday is.
好了  现在有点晚了
Okay, running a little late.
只能在车里给你化妆了
Gonna have to paint your face in the car.
耶  我好高兴诶
Yay, I'm the winner.
祝我好运吧  查莉
Wish me good luck, Charlie.
-嘿  老妈  -噢  我的小乖乖
-Hey, mom. -Oh, there's my little tyke.
你好呀
How ya doin'?
老妈  你没事吧
Mom, you feeling okay?
相当超级以及非常的好
Super good and gettin' better.
你怎么这样说话
Why are you talking like that?
怎样说话
Like what?
噢  有件趣事
Oh funny thing.
今天我和黛比·杜利一起去上蜡褪毛
I was taking a wax today with Debbie Dooley.
然后我们发现了一种神奇的药剂
And we found a magic potion.
然后  我们自然的就各自抿了一小口
Well, naturally we each took a sip,
但是没任何反应
But nothing happened.
呃  老妈
Uh, mom,
有反应了
Something did happen.
我们需要解决一下
We need to fix this.
没什么需要解决的  管家婆先生
Nothing to fix, Mr. Bossy pants.
要小饼干吗
Snickerdoodle?
噢  好吧  你说的没错  我们没事了
Oh yeah, you're right. We are good.
是吗
Are we?
那还用说
You betcha.